Privacy Policy
--------------

This privacy policy may be changed at any time.

Agreement relating to confidentiality.

#### Email addresses recording

Our server stores the email addresses of Users during registration for internal purposes only. Under no circumstances, we will rent, sell, or send personal data's to third parties.

#### IP Addresses recording and their approximative geolocations

Our servers can detect the IP Address of Users connection through the Internet. These IP addresses (public) and their approximative geolocations are recorded by our servers for internal use only (registration on the site, optimal use of downloads, protection against thieves, etc.).

#### Use of cookies

We use cookies for Users convenience by saving the connection to the site (thus avoiding unnecessary reconnections). We do not use tracking methods.

#### Payment Informations

All payments made on our website are managed by outside firms. Payments are secure and encrypted, in any case these companies can not save Users banking information.

#### Exceptional disclosure of personal data

We may be required to disclose Users personal data in order to protect our legal rights or where disclosure of Users personal data's are required of us by the judicial authorities only when legal procedures are followed.

#### Datalogging

Files links that Users download are stored in a database for legal concerns and our internal use. All saved links are erased within 1 month for security reasons and service needs. However all requests made on our site are stored for 1 year, the legal retention period.

Language: [** English (US)**](#) [...](https://real-debrid.com/ajax/lang.php)

© 2009-2024 Real-Debrid, All Rights Reserved - [Privacy Policy](https://real-debrid.com/privacy) - [Legal](https://real-debrid.com/legal) - [Terms Of Services](https://real-debrid.com/terms) - [Abuse](https://real-debrid.com/abuse)B2 (4.59ms)
